egreetings.com 2010-02-25

# Find out more about Egreetings.com!

| 

## Last updated: November 2008

### GENERAL MATTERS

**Overview**

At the Egreetings.com Network ("Egreetings.com"), protecting our users' privacy and security is a top priority. For this reason, we have adopted the following policy to advise you of your choices regarding the use of your personal information online. This policy describes what types of information we gather about you, how we use it, under what circumstances we disclose it to third-parties, and your rights to update or correct it. 

**Scope of Policy**

This Policy applies to Egreetings.com, a member of the AmericanGreetings.com ("AG") network of sites. It does not apply to other companies' or organizations' web sites to which we link. You should carefully review the privacy policies of those web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information. 

#### INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

#### Information Gathered From All Visitors 

**Aggregate Data**

We gather certain generic information with respect to customers' use of our web site, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the areas on the web site that they favor. These statistics are very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use this type of data in aggregate-that is, we look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us determine the extent to which our customers use certain parts of our web site, which, in turn, enables us to make it as appealing as possible. We may also provide statistical "ratings" about how our customers collectively use our web site to advertisers, sponsors, and other companies with which we do business ("Business Partners"). We do this so they, too, can understand how often people use their areas of the site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience. These statistical ratings do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users. 

**Cookies**

We use a technology nicknamed "cookies" on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. For example, cookies allow us to recognize you when you re-enter our web site so that you will not have to sign-in each time you visit. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser to notify you when you've received a cookie or, alternatively, to refuse to accept cookies. It is important to note that you may not be able to use certain features on our web site if you choose not to accept cookies, such as automatic sign-in, address book, outbox, and reminders. In addition, you will not be able to participate in any of our sweepstakes or contests. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. 

**Third Party Advertiser Cookies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Internet. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and Clear Gif technology (aka 1x1 Pixel .gifs, Web bugs) to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. Egreetings.com does not use or have access to this information. 

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt out or visit the web site of the National Advertising Initiative ("NAI") to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies' privacy policies. 

**Advertising Research Cookies.**

From time-to-time, outside third party research companies may set cookies on your browser regarding exposure to certain ad placements. These cookies may be used later for research purposes if you later opt-in to take a survey. If you choose to take the survey, these companies may examine your browser to see if a one of their cookies has been set. If the company detects the cookie in your browser, it will gather only 2 pieces of information from it: where you have seen a particular ad and; how many times you have seen it. If you do not want these kinds of cookies to be set to your browser, you can opt-out by [clicking here](http://ch.questionmarket.com/site/subnav/optout.html). 

**Advertising Targeting Cookies**  
From time to time, we may use cookies to track your exposure to certain areas of the site (such as Pets, Birthday, etc.). These cookies may be used later to target advertising on our site to your interests. No personally identifiable information is collected through these cookies, and the data collected with these cookies is not shared with third parties. If you do not want these kinds of cookies set to your browser, you can opt-out by clicking here. 

**IP Addresses**

We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message. 

Egreetings.com INCLUDES THE SENDER IP ADDRESS IN THE HEADER INFORMATION OF EACH ECARD NOTIFICATION E-MAIL IT SENDS. IT IS AVAILABLE TO THE ECARD RECIPIENT AND ANYONE ELSE WHO IS FORWARDED THE NOTIFICATION E-MAIL. THIS LIMITS YOUR ABILITY TO COMMUNICATE ANONYMOUSLY USING ELECTRONIC ECARDS. ELECTRONIC ECARDS ARE NEITHER INTENDED NOR APPROPRIATE FOR ANONYMOUS COMMUNICATIONS, AND SUCH ACTIVITY IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED BY THE ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY IN OUR [TERMS OF SERVICE](http://www.egreetings.com/legal.pd). 

**When You Send An eCard**

If you use our web site to send an eCard or any other content, we collect your e-mail address and your recipient's e-mail address. This information is necessary to send the content and provide confirmation that it has been received. We will not use your recipient's e-mail address for any purpose other than to send the eCard. We may also use your e-mail address to contact you if you have chosen to receive communications from Egreetings.com or its Partners. (See Opt-Out/Changing Your Status, below). 

**Personalizing Your Experience on the Web Site**

We try to personalize your experience on our web sites by tracking eCards and other content you have sent and gifts you have purchased in order to shape our recommendations about the eCards, games, and gifts that might be of interest to you. We also examine customer traffic patterns and web site usage to help us enhance the design and layout of the site and make it easier to navigate. 

From time to time, we may send you surveys or solicit your feedback. We use surveys to gauge user interest in new products and premiums we may offer. We will ask for your feedback on eCards and other site features. We will use the information we gather to improve our sites and provide a more meaningful experience for our users. We may also use the information to alert you to offers and products in which you have expressed an interest. 

#### The eGreetings Toolbar

The Toolbar automatically sends only standard, limited information to AGCM, which may be retained in AGCM's server logs. It does not send any information about the web pages you visit (e.g., the URL).

**GUIDs**

Your copy of the eGreetings Toolbar includes a unique application number (a "GUID"). When you install the eGreetings Toolbar, this number and a message indicating whether the installation succeeded are sent back to eGreetings. Also, when the eGreetings Toolbar automatically checks to see if a new version is available, the current version number and the unique application number are sent to AGCM. The GUID is required for the eGreetings Toolbar to work and cannot be disabled. 

We also tag each toolbar with a GUID, which tracks your activity and the search terms you insert into the toolbar. Again, this information is not tied to any personally identifiable information about you. 

**Search Queries**

The eGreetings Toolbar, in the course of processing a given search query, sends a request to our servers. This request includes the keyword query, time of day, browser type, default language setting, IP address, the GUID, and a code that identifies the marketing or distribution source of the toolbar used by you to conduct your search. If the search query is being generated as the result of a misspelled URL or search term entered in to the browser address bar, we also receive the misspelled URL address or search term. We use this information in order to properly process your search request. For example, this data provides us with: information on which language you prefer to use; aggregated click information for the purpose of ensuring that our search partners are appropriately compensating us; information that allows us to make accurate payments to our distributors; aggregated usage and retention information; and aggregated search query information for the purpose of further monetizing commercially oriented search keywords. **All information collected from a search query is recorded on a non-personally identifiable basis and is kept strictly anonymous.** In addition, all information about search activity is evaluated only on an aggregate basis (excepted in response to a customer service inquiry or legal process). 

**Partnership with Microsoft**

As a Microsoft Live partner, any personally identifiable information we collect will be jointly owned by eGreetings and Microsoft Corporation. For information about Microsoft Corporation's privacy practices go to the MSN privacy statement. 

**Communications from Egreetings.com**

We send to all of our users our exclusive Egreetings.com Newsletter, which alerts you to new features, content, and services, premiums available on our site. From time to time, we will also send you invitations to enhance your Egreetings.com membership, offers for new services from Egreetings.com, special "Members Only" premiums, or special offers from our affiliates and sponsors. These communications are sent to you directly by Egreetings.com. We do not share your personally identifiable information with any third parties in connection with the Newsletter. 

You can always decline the Newsletter by un-checking the opt-out box on the "Personalize this eCard" pages or registration pages on our site. If you are already receiving the Newsletter and you want to unsubscribe, you can simply follow the "unsubscribe" links at the bottom of each edition. For other ways to unsubscribe, see Opt-Out/Changing Your Status, below. 

**Communications from Our Business Partners**

Egreetings.com also offers you the opportunity to receive money-saving offers, discounts, and promotions from our Business Partners. These communications may come from Egreetings.com or directly from the Partners themselves. We may also share with them certain demographic, geographic, preference, and other personally identifiable information we have gathered about you. This will help them in directing to you offers that are more likely to be of interest. 

This program is conducted strictly on an opt-in basis. In order to receive the offers, you must affirmatively check the clearly marked box on our "Personalize this eCard" pages and registration pages on our site. If you leave the box unchecked, you will not receive any offers. If you do sign up for the program but later change your mind, you are free at any time to opt-out by following the procedures outlined in Opt-Out/Changing Your Status, below. 

**Mandatory Communications**

Egreetings.com reserves the right to communicate with you from time to time about important administrative, policy, legal, credit card, and billing matters, which will affect your use of our web sites, including without limitation any alleged violations of our [Terms of Service](http://www.egreetings.com/legal.pd). These communications are mandatory. 

**Information Gathered From Members**

If you elect to purchase Membership on Egreetings.com, you will be required to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, e-mail address, phone number, credit card number, expiration date, and billing address (this required information is subject to change from time to time). There will also be opportunities for you to provide us with additional information regarding your preferences and interests. This information, however, is not required and is completely optional on your part. 

Additional data may be collected from Members based upon certain services they elect to utilize on our web site. For example, we may track the categories of eCards you send in order to make appropriate recommendations for products or services available on our site or those of our Business Partners. Members may register for Egreetings.com Reminders, which are e-mail alerts to track important dates and occasions they specify. The Egreetings.com address book feature allows Members to store addresses of friends and family in order to make sending an eCard even easier. By obtaining this information, we can provide our Members with specific content and advertising in which they might be interested. None of this information is required to use our service or to become a Member; however, the omission of certain types of data will limit the value of your membership. 

If you become an Unlimited Member of Egreetings.com from one of our co-branded sites, we may share your registration information with the co-branded partner. In such instances, the site will be clearly labeled with the branding information of our partner and links to its privacy policy will be conspicuously posted. 

**Egreetings.com' USES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If you have provided us your consent, we will use the information we have collected about you in five ways:

  1. To send personalized, targeted information that we think our users will find relevant, either from Egreetings.com or directly from its Business Partners; 
  2. To include targeted advertising within such messages; 
  3. To send promotions and coupons based on the user's interests; 
  4. To contact the user for feedback and surveys; and 
  5. To send the user other information about Egreetings.com. 

**On-Site Advertising**

Egreetings.com may also use information about you to target advertising while you are visiting our site. For example, we may serve ads from toy companies to users searching the Kids Birthday eCard pages. We may also use geographic or other information we have collected from you to make sure that the ads you see are for goods and services that are actually of interest to you or are available in your area. We may use cookie files to assure that you will not be served the same ads repeatedly. 

**Information Sharing Between Affiliates**

Egreetings.com is a member of the American Greetings family. This means it is an Affiliate of American Greetings and its subsidiaries, including but not limited to AmericanGreetings.com, BlueMountain.com, Midiringtones.com, HatterChatter.com, BloomByAG.com, Carlton Cards Retail, Inc., Plus Mark, Inc., Gibson, Guildhouse, and DesignWare. Egreetings.com reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information, including your email, postal address, phone number and purchase history, with its Affiliates. We may share your personally identifiable information with Affiliates in order to conduct promotions, offer special premiums, and share databases and equipment. We will not share your credit card information with anyone, including Affiliates, without your express permission. We reserve the right to share your information with other companies that become Affiliates of Egreetings.com. 

**Third Party Information Sharing**

Generally, we do not share your information with third parties. We do reserve the right to share your information with third party companies we may use to offer premiums, maintain subscriptions and perform other service functions. We do not share equipment or databases with these companies and will not share your credit card information with them without your express permission. Additionally, any company we use will not share, sell, distribute or use your information except to provide us services. 

**Order Fulfillment**

From time to time, you may be given the opportunity to order products and services directly on the Egreetings.com site, the Newsletters, or in other communications you may receive from Egreetings.com. These orders are typically fulfilled by Egreetings.com' Business Partners directly. To process your order, Egreetings.com may provide these Partners with your name, street address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information. Egreetings.com will limit the types of information shared to the minimum necessary to efficiently process your order. However, in accepting these offers, you become a customer of the Business Partner and therefore subject to its privacy policy. Egreetings.com will alert users whenever a Business Partner will be fulfilling an order for products or services ordered on our site. We encourage you to review these companies' privacy policies and only do business with those who adhere to personal information practices with which you are comfortable. 

**Privacy of eCard Information**

We treat all of our eCards products as private correspondence between the sender and the recipient and will not disclose the contents of any eCard other than to the intended recipient, except under the specific situations outlined in Disclosure Exceptions, below. 

This policy applies to all aspects of our eCards, including your personalized messages, and attached photos or graphics. Under normal circumstances, we will not monitor or edit the contents of the eCards you send. On occasion, however, we may need to view your message in connection with the technical processing of your eCard or the maintenance of our network. Also, if you ask one of our customer support representatives to help you send an eCard or to verify that an eCard was sent, that representative will be able to access all information about the eCard, including the recipient's e-mail address and the message. 

**Disclosure Exceptions**

Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third-parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary: 

  * To comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; 
  * To protect the company's rights and property; 
  * To investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive messages; 
  * To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web site and/or the Egreetings.com service; or 
  * During emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk. 

Your IP address can be accessed by eCard recipients in the header of the notification e-mail. Under certain circumstances, recipients, their legal representatives, and/or law enforcement authorities may be able to combine this with information disclosed by ISPs to determine the source of a particular communication. By using this service, you knowingly and voluntarily assume any risks associated with such disclosure. 

#### YOUR CONTROL OVER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

**Opt-Out/Changing Your Status**

At any time, you can change choices you have previously made as to the use of your personal information. Every communication Egreetings.com sends you will contain a clearly worded "Opt-Out" or "Unsubscribe" link allowing you to withdraw your permission for future mailings. Alternatively, you can send a blank e-mail to [nomail@privacy.Egreetings.com](mailto:nomail@privacy.Egreetings.com) and type "unsubscribe" in the subject field. This system is automated and must be contacted from the email address you wish to have removed. Permission changes will be honored as soon as possible after receipt. Please allow 5 to 7 days for processing. Permission changes will not affect any information which you provided to us and which we previously shared with our Business Partners. 

**Editing Your Profile**

If you are a Member, you have the ability to review and correct your personally identifiable information at any time. Simply click the "My Account" link at the top of each page. From there, you can change your address information, e-mail type, sign-in, and e-mail permissions. You can revise, add, delete, or completely cancel all alerts by clicking the "Reminder" links on the headers of each page. 

**California Residents.**  
As of January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors to this Site who are residents of California to request information regarding AG's disclosure of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to our Customer Support center at [help@aginteractive.com](mailto:help@aginteractive.com).

#### OTHER MATTERS

**Protection For Children - COPPA Compliance**

We are committed to protecting the privacy and rights of children online. We believe that children should be able to use the Internet in a safe, productive, and efficient manner and should be afforded the highest protection available with respect to their personal information. To that end, we have made it our policy to not collect any individually identifiable information from users whom we know are under the age of 13. Our registration process blocks the registration of users under 13 years old and will automatically delete all individually identifiable information collected from such users. 

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") imposes certain requirements upon web sites and online services that are directed toward children. To learn more about COPPA, [click here](http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm) for the Federal Trade Commission COPPA Web Site. 

**Contests and Promotions**

Occasionally, Egreetings.com may sponsor contests and/or promotions on our sites or in our e-mail products. Participation in such contests is purely voluntary. In order to enter a contest or promotion, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information. By entering, you agree to all of its terms and conditions, which will be clearly outlined in the rules. Where a contest or promotion is not sponsored by Egreetings.com, the identity of the sponsor will be clearly disclosed in the rules. Egreetings.com cannot be responsible for actions or policies of third-party contest sponsors. Users are encouraged to review the relevant privacy policy of the sponsor before entering. 

**Sale of Assets**

In the event that Egreetings.com and/or its units or subsidiaries are ever sold, acquired, merged, liquidated, reorganized, or otherwise transferred, we reserve the right to transfer our user databases together with any personally identifiable information contained therein, to a third-party acquiring Egreetings.com' assets. In the event we do so, we will place a prominent notice of the sale on the homepage of our site, with links to information as to how you can change your privacy preferences. 

**Data Security**

When you place orders for purchased products or access your payment information, we use an advanced encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to protect the storage and transfer of your data from unauthorized parties. While on a secure page, such as our registration form, a lock or key icon appears on the bottom of your web browser. 

In addition to our online security efforts, we take steps to protect your personal data offline, as well. All of your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Employees are granted access on a need-to-know basis (for example, our billing clerk or a customer support representative). Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

Egreetings.com' main servers are operated from a dedicated Internet hosting facility with state-of-the-art physical security features, including smoke detection and fire suppression systems, motion sensors, and 24x7 secured access, as well as video camera surveillance and security breach alarms. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Egreetings.com will occasionally update this Privacy Policy in response to changing business circumstances and legal developments. When Egreetings.com posts changes to this Policy, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of Egreetings.com Sites. If there are material changes to this Policy or in how Egreetings.com uses your personally identifiable information, Egreetings.com will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Egreetings.com encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information. 

**USE COMMON SENSE IN ALL YOUR ONLINE ACVITIVITIES**

Even the best policy can't protect your online privacy and security in all circumstances. Unscrupulous advertisers, hackers, and scam artists are constantly searching the Internet looking for new targets. Your best protection is to understand the limits to privacy on the Internet and use common sense in all of your on-line activities. 

Be aware that e-mail is an inherently insecure form of communication. Remember that third parties are sometimes able to illegally intercept your unencrypted messages, including eCards. 

Anytime you visit a chat room or post a message to an on-line bulletin board, your e-mail address can be accessed by advertisers looking to compile lists for unsolicited commercial e-mail (also known as spam). Be sure that you only disclose your e-mail address in circumstances in which it is safe to do so. 

Beware of scams in which persons unknown to you request your screen name, password, or credit card information. Make sure you verify the identity of anyone asking for personal information. 

Always monitor your children's on-line activities and educate them as to the rules for safe Internet use. For more information, [click here](http://www.getnetwise.org/) for the Internet Education Foundation's Online Safety Guide for Kids. 

If you have any questions, please feel free to review our [help center](http://www.egreetings.com/customer/index.pd). 

|
